tapfortap.com 2017-06-06

# Pretio Interactive

← GO BACK

## Pretio Interactive Privacy Policy

Pretio Interactive Inc. (“Pretio Interactive”, “we”, “us” or “our”) knows you care about how personal information is used and shared, and we take your privacy seriously. We have adopted this Privacy Policy to explain how Pretio Interactive collects, stores, and uses the information collected in connection with Pretio Interactive’s products and services.

By visiting, accessing or using Pretio Interactive’s services, including the rewards service our websites and any other linked pages, features, content, mobile applications, application services (collectively, the "Service"), or third-party integrations, you acknowledge that you accept the practices outlined in this Privacy Policy.

If this privacy policy is not acceptable to you, you should not use or cease to use the service. This Privacy Policy is incorporated into and forms part of Pretio Interactive’s Terms of Service which are available at [http://terms.pretio.in/.](http://terms.pretio.in/)

### What Does This Privacy Policy Cover?

By visiting the Website or using the Service this Privacy Policy covers information you may submit to Pretio Interactive, including your name, email address, reward gifts (“Gifts”) you send and receive, and other data you generate while using Service or the Website. It also covers information that we gather automatically when you use the Service or our Website, including your IP address, browser type, cookie information, and browsing patterns.

This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that Pretio Interactive does not own or control, or to individuals that Pretio Interactive does not employ or manage.

### Personal Information You Provide to Us

We receive and store any information you enter through the Service or provide to us in any other way.

The types of information we collect include your name, email address, browser or mobile device information, and any other information necessary for us to provide the Service.

The information you provide is used to help you receive personalized Gifts, customize the content and advertising you see, and to communicate with you about specials and new features. We also draw upon this information to better adapt the Service to your needs, to research the effectiveness of our network, and to develop new products and services.

### Personal Information Collected Automatically

Pretio Interactive automatically receives and stores information from your browser including your IP address, Media Access Control (“MAC”) address and unique device identifier or other persistent or non-persistent device identifier (“Device ID”), device software platform and firmware, geographical data such as zip code, postal code, area code and location, cookie information, and browsing patterns. 

Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that we transfer to your computer through your browser to recognize your browser and tell us how and when you access the Service or visit pages on our Website. You have the option to disable cookies by changing the options in your browser to stop accepting cookies or to prompt you before accepting a cookie from the pages you visit. We recommend that you leave cookies activated, however, because cookies are needed in order to use the Service.

Pretio Interactive uses cookie and other browsing data in aggregate form to track Website usage and improve your experience. We may provide usage information to our partners in order to help them understand how often people use their services and our Website. Pretio Interactive never discloses information to a partner in a manner that would identify you personally.

We share your Personal Information only as described in this Privacy Policy. In order to ensure your privacy is protected, Pretio Interactive does not share your personal information unless we have:

  1. received your permission to share your personal information;
  2. Given you notice that we will share your personal information, such as by telling you about in this Privacy Policy; or
  3. removed your name and any other personally identifying information from it.

_Advertisers:_ Pretio Interactive Inc. allows advertisers to choose the demographic information of users who will see their advertisements and you agree that we may use any of the information we have collected from you to select or allow the advertiser to select the appropriate audience for those advertisements. For example, we may allow an advertiser to target an ad to you based on your reward redemption history, demographics, location and/or application usage history.

_Affiliated Businesses We Do Not Control:_ We are affiliated with a variety of businesses, including merchants who supply the Gifts and rewards we make available to you, and work closely with these businesses to deliver the Service. In certain situations, these businesses sell items to you through the Service and particularly through e-mails you may consent to receive from these businesses. In other situations, Pretio Interactive provides services or sells products jointly with affiliated businesses. You can easily recognize when an affiliated business is associated with a transaction, and we will share your personal information with that affiliated business that is related to the transaction you have entered into.

_Agents:_ We employ other companies and people to help us deliver the Service and need to share your information with them. Unless we tell you differently, Pretio Interactive’s agents do not have any right to use the Personal Information we share with them beyond what is necessary to assist us to deliver our products and services. You hereby consent to our sharing your personal information for the above purposes.

_Promotional Offers sent by Pretio Interactive:_ We may send offers to you on behalf of other businesses. However, when we do so, we do not give the other business your Personal Information. If you do not wish to receive these offers, you will have the option to unsubscribe using a link found at the bottom of the email. We may provide certain of your Personal Information to third parties if you affirmatively allow us to do so by opting in to an offer we make to you.

_Promotional Offers sent by Third Parties:_ We partner with third parties who use Pretio Interactive to send promotions to their current customers via email, social media, and other means. If you are directed to Pretio Interactive as a result of a third-party campaign, we may share certain Personal Information with the third party who referred you. You hereby consent to our sharing of Personal Information in such cases and acknowledge that such information may be retained by the third party even if you delete your Pretio Interactive account.

_Business Transfers:_ In some cases, Pretio Interactive may undergo a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of all or a portion of its assets. In these types of transactions, customer information is typically one of the business assets that is transferred. Moreover, if Pretio Interactive, or substantially all of its assets were acquired, or in the unlikely event that Pretio Interactive goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, customer information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer of Pretio Interactive may continue to use your Personal Information as set forth in this policy.

_Protection of Pretio Interactive and Others:_ We may release personal information to appropriate third parties when we believe in good faith that we are required to do so by law or we believe that such action is necessary in order (a) to comply with legal processes such as a search warrant, subpoena, court order or in connection with litigation, (b) to protect Pretio Interactive’s rights and property, (c) to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, including intellectual property infringement, fraud, or situations involving potential threats to the rights, property, or personal safety of any person, or (d) to protect against misuse or unauthorized use of the Service. 

_With Your Consent:_ Except as set forth above, you will be notified when your personal information may be shared with third parties, and will be able to prevent the sharing of this information.

### Is My Personal Information Secure?

Pretio Interactive endeavors to ensure that personal information is kept secure and has in place industry standard security infrastructure and processes to do so. However, because transmission of data over the Internet cannot be completely secure, Pretio Interactive cannot guarantee that unauthorized access, hacking, data loss, or other breaches will never occur. 

### How Can I Change or Remove Personal Information You Have Provided to Pretio Interactive?

If you believe that your personal information that we have is incorrect or you wish to remove personal information, please e-mail Pretio Interactive at support@pretiointeractive.com and we will assist you. Please note that we may retain an archived copy of your records as required by law or for legitimate business purposes.

### Children

The Service is not intended for children under the age of 18 and we do not knowingly collect any personal Information from such children. If we discover that we have inadvertently collected personal Information from children, we will take all reasonable measures to erase such information from our systems and records as soon as possible.

### Outside Websites and Links

The Service contains links to outside sources, such as third party websites, other online services or offers from third parties, such as third party advertisers or merchants. If you choose to participate in a reward offer or ‘click’ an advertisement or other third party link, you may be directed to that third party’s website or service and/or be prompted to provide personal information. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such third party websites or services, including our merchants. If you have any questions about how these third party websites or services use your information, you should review their policies or contact them directly.

### Changes To This Privacy Policy

Pretio Interactive reserves the right to modify this Privacy Policy from time to time and will post a current version of the Privacy Policy at [http://privacy.pretio.in/.](http://privacy.pretio.in/) By continuing to access or use the Service after a modification, you are agreeing to be bound by the modified Privacy Policy. 

### Questions Or Concerns

If you have any questions or concerns regarding privacy at Pretio Interactive, please send a detailed message to support@pretiointeractive.com.
